Finding Aid for francisco
Clarke Historical Library
- Francisco Photography Studio Photographic Collection is open for research.
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sloan, Dorotha, Mrs. - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sloan, Dorotha, Mrs. - Jim Powell Family,undated (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sloan, Raymond - Couple,May 11, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Slocum, Emily - Moerlin,undated (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Slocum, John,November 30, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 101)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Small, Donna,undated (Box 6, Folder 102)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Small, John - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 103)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smalley, Clarence - 9-month-old Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smalley, Earl - Baby Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smiley, Alec,undated (Box 6, Folder 106)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Beulah,August 8, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 107)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Carl and Son - 8-year-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 108)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Chas. and Wife,undated (Box 6, Folder 109)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Eva Marie, Mrs. Marvin - Copy (John Peters),undated (Box 6, Folder 110)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Gerald and Wife,June 7, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 111)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Gladys - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 112)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Grace,undated (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Harry, Jr.,undated (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, J.P.,undated (Box 6, Folder 115)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Jessie, Mrs.,undated (Box 6, Folder 116)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, John,undated (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Joyce - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Larry - 11-month-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Leon,undated (Box 6, Folder 120)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Lorraine,undated (Box 6, Folder 121)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Lucy,undated (Box 6, Folder 122)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Margaret,undated (Box 6, Folder 123)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Mary,September 7, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Orville,January 7, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 125)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Ralph,undated (Box 6, Folder 126)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Robt. - 7-month-old Girl,undated (Box 6, Folder 127)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Roy,undated (Box 6, Folder 128)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Ruth Ann,July 7, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 129)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Sheryl,June 21, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Ula's Mother, Mrs.,undated (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, Walter,undated (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Smith, William, Harrison, Michigan,undated (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Soloman, Abraham,undated (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sommer, Norm,undated (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Soners, Roy,November 25, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sorola, Wm.,undated (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sowles, Larry,undated (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Speckled Trout Record, 1922 - a Man,1922 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Spence, Patricia - 4-month-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Spence,Sandra - 10-month-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Spencer, Chas. A.,undated (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Spencer, H. - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Spencer, Roy,undated (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Spiris, Geo,undated (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Spitsberger, J.E.,undated (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sponseller, Vern, Mrs.,undated (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sprague, Jai,undated (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sprague, Ralph,undated (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Springer, Lester - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sprogue, Joe,undated (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stacy, G.,undated (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Staley, Don,undated (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Starner, Glen and Wife,May 11, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Staveley, Jane,undated (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Staveley, Janice,undated (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stebelton, J. - Baby,undated (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Steven, Carol,undated (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stevens, Ada,undated (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stockham, Wm.,undated (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stockes, Jerry,undated (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Storrs, Herbert,undated (Box 6, Folder 162)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Straka, Dick,undated (Box 6, Folder 163)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Straley, Robert and Wife,undated (Box 6, Folder 164)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stramm, Carl,undated (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Strang, Laurence G. - Copy of Marriage License,July 9, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Straus, Max - 14-month-old Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Strauss, Ann,undated (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Streeter, Wilburt,undated (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Strehl, Harry and Wife,February 19, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stren, Fred - 9-month-old (2),June 18, 1966; August 5, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Strong, Alson,undated (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Strong, Ray - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Strong, Stella,undated (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stroup, Joyce,undated (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Struble, Sid,undated (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stuber, Pauline,undated (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Studer, [no first name],undated (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Stutting, Sandra,undated (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sutton, Jan,undated (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sutton, Shellie,undated (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swain, Fred T.,November 4, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swan, Alice Dowell,undated (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swan, Bob - Baby Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swan, Francis, Jr.,undated (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swan, H., Mrs.,undated (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sweet, Bert - Copy, Family,undated (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sweet, Bertrand,undated (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swett, Joy,undated (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swety, Joe - Baby,undated (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Swetzer, Deek,undated (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Switzer, Jim,undated (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Switzer, John,undated (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sygaisano, Gloria C. and Doctor,April 21, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Sytek, Theodor,undated (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tanner, Irene,undated (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tayler, Lewis,undated (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Taylor, Carol,undated (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Taylor, Dona,undated (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Taylor, Phyliss,undated (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Taylor, Russell,undated (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Taylor, W.J.,undated (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Taylor, Wm. J. and Wife,December 2, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Teeter, Herman,undated (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Teixeria, Arthur,undated (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Telmann, Roy - 1- and 4-year-olds,1959 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thaller, Linda S.,July 30, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thayer, Wallace,undated (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theilen, Betty,undated (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theisen, Diane,undated (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theisen, Genevieve - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theisen, Jack,November 23, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theisen, John - 3-year-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theisen, Mrs. Mike and Baby,March 11, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theisen, Richard - Bonnie,undated (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Theradakorh, Ravelorh - Application,undated (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, Bill,undated (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, Don - Academy Senior,1963 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, Elmer - Family Photograph,undated (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, Helen,undated (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, John,October 20, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, Marilyn,undated (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, Ray,undated (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Thering, Raymond, Jr.,September 27, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Therman, A. - 1-year-old Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tilmann, Dale - 3 Children,November 4, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tilmann, Patricia,undated (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tilmann, Philomena,March 24, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tilmann, Roy - 1-year-old Girl,July 28, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Timpe, Donald - 8-month-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Todd, George,July 7, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Todink, Mrs., Sr. - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tope, John,August 7, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Torpey, Hilton,undated (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Torpey, Jack - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Torpey, Leo - 1-year-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Torpey, Susan - Copy Negatives,April 2, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Torres, Dan - 14-month-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Toth, Marie - Baby Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 239)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Trainor, Jack,undated (Box 6, Folder 240)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Travis, Barbara,undated (Box 6, Folder 241)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Trevisol, Carol,undated (Box 6, Folder 242)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tripp, Sally M.,October 22, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 243)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tromblay, Arthur W. (2),February 28, 1949; March 1, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 244)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tromblay, Arthur W.,July 7, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tromblay, Effie,February 28, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Trout - 8 pound with a Man,undated (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Truhlor, Lillian,undated (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Trumbley, E., Mrs.,undated (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tully, Vince,undated (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tupper, Mary Lou - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Turck, [no first name],undated (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Twig, Phylis,undated (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Twindlehurst, Jeaneen,undated (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tyler, Dorothy - 8-month-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Tyler, Richard,undated (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Ulbrich, John,undated (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Upper Peninsula (U.P.) Trip with Jack Brewser,1932 (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, U.S. Granger,undated (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Utterback, Walt,undated (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Valentine, Mary,undated (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanArker, Harry and Wife,undated (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanBuskirk, Nola,undated (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanCoppenalle, Mary - Passport,undated (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanDecar, Jim,undated (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Vanderwoude, Louise,undated (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanHorn, Forrest - 2 Children,undated (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanHorn, Fred - Wedding,undated (Box 6, Folder 268)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanLien, M. - 2 Children,undated (Box 6, Folder 269)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanNostrand, Howard - Wedding,undated (Box 6, Folder 270)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanOrden, Betty,undated (Box 6, Folder 271)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanOrden, Helen,undated (Box 6, Folder 272)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VanOrden, Shirley,undated (Box 6, Folder 273)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Veit, John, Mrs. - Grace,undated (Box 6, Folder 274)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Veit, Stanley - 1-year-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 275)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Verleger, Frank,October 28, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 276)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Vernon, Raymond,undated (Box 6, Folder 277)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Verwey, Andrew - Mr. and Mrs.,April 22, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 278)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Verwey, F.J. - 4-month-old,undated (Box 6, Folder 279)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Verwey, Joe,undated (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Verwey, John,undated (Box 6, Folder 281)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Verwey, Mary Ann,undated (Box 6, Folder 282)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Verwey, Mo. - Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 283)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Viet, Gary,undated (Box 6, Folder 284)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Vodicka, Billie,undated (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Vodicka, Robt, - 1.5 - old girl,undated (Box 6, Folder 286)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Vogel, Jim,undated (Box 6, Folder 287)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Voisin, Ed,undated (Box 6, Folder 288)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Voisin, Leo,undated (Box 6, Folder 289)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Voisin, Norma,undated (Box 6, Folder 290)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VonDoloski, Margaret - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 291)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, VonDoloski, Walter - 7-year-old Boy,undated (Box 6, Folder 292)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Wagner, John - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 293)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Wagner, Virginia - 3 copies, October 23, 1964; 2 Copies July 25, 1969,October 23, 1964; July 25, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 294)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Waldorf, Bill,undated (Box 6, Folder 295)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walker, Ann - 2 Children,December 2,1967 (Box 6, Folder 296)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walker, Frank,undated (Box 6, Folder 297)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walker, John,undated (Box 6, Folder 298)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walker, Mike,undated (Box 6, Folder 299)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Wallace, Billie Lee - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 300)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walleyes - Three Men,undated (Box 6, Folder 301)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walters, M.L.,undated (Box 6, Folder 302)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walton, Leon, Mrs.,undated (Box 6, Folder 303)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Walton, Myrtle - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 304)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Wang, Tong-eng,undated (Box 6, Folder 305)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Ward, Bob,undated (Box 6, Folder 306)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Ward, Esther - 1-year-old Girl,undated (Box 6, Folder 307)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Ward, Roger - 1-year-old,1963 (Box 6, Folder 308)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Warner, Bob,undated (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Warner, Ronald - Baby Girl,undated (Box 6, Folder 310)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Watson, Bev,undated (Box 6, Folder 311)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Watson, Don and Anne Mayville,undated (Box 6, Folder 312)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Watson, Janette - serviceman,undated (Box 6, Folder 313)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Watson, Lloyd,undated (Box 6, Folder 314)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Watson, Ruth,undated (Box 6, Folder 315)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Watson, Sally,undated (Box 6, Folder 316)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Watts, Robt., Mrs. - Copy,undated (Box 6, Folder 317)
  - 3.5 x 4.5 inch Negatives, S-Z, Right side of the box, Weaver, Jess,December 21, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 318)